gamesbox.com 2012-09-20

# Webmasters FLASH - Play Free Flash Games Online at GamesBox.com GamesBox.com - Free Flash Games - Play Your Favorite Game Online Right Now!

At GamesBox.com, we recognize that privacy of your personal information is important. Here is information on what types of personal information we receive and collect when you visit GamesBox.com, and how we safeguard your information. We never sell your personal information to third parties.

**Log Files**  
As with most other websites, we collect and use the data contained in log files. The information in the log files include your IP (internet protocol) address, your ISP, the browser you used to visit our site (such as Internet Explorer or Firefox), the time you visited our site and which pages you visited throughout our site.

**Cookies and Web Beacons**  
We do use cookies to store information, such as your commenting preferences when you visit our site. We also use third party advertisements on GamesBox.com to support our site. Some of these advertisers may use technology such as cookies and web beacons when they advertise on our site, which will also send these advertisers (such as Google through the Google AdSense program) information including your IP address, your ISP, the browser you used to visit our site, and in some cases, whether you have Flash installed. This is generally used for geotargeting purposes (showing New York real estate ads to someone in New York, for example) or showing certain ads based on specific sites visited (such as showing cooking ads to someone who frequents cooking sites).

You can choose to disable or selectively turn off our cookies or third-party cookies in your browser settings, or by managing preferences in your security software. However, this can affect how you are able to interact with our site as well as other websites. This could include the inability to log into services or programs, such as logging into forums or accounts.

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on GamesBox.com. Google’s use of the [DoubleClick DART cookie](http://www.doubleclick.com/privacy/faq.aspx) enables it to serve ads to you based on your visit to this site and other sites on the Internet. You may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

We have contracted with ValueClick to monitor certain pages of our website for the purpose of reporting website traffic, statistics, ValueClick advertisement ‘click-throughs’, and/or other activities on our website. Where authorized by us, ValueClick and its business partners may use cookies, web beacons, and/or other monitoring technologies to compile anonymous statistics about our website visitors. No personally identifiable information is collected by or transferred to any party other than the ValueClick advertiser. For more information about how the information is collected and used by ValueClick, please see the [ValueClick’s privacy policy](http://www.valueclickmedia.com/member_privacy.shtml). To opt out of such collection and use, visit [Network Advertising Initiative opt-out page](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp).
